A Finding Aid to the Dimitri Hadzi Papers, 1910s-2007, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Audiovisual Material, 1952-2000; Series 13; Archival Resource Key; 12 Linear feet Box 26-40
  - Miscellaneous, Archival Resource Key
    - Acetato, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel 5 inch (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Giacimenti, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Fireworks, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel 5 inch (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Fischer Concert, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel 5 inch (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Videocassettes (BetacamSP) (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified, 1981 December 10; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified, undated; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Notes and Photographs of Original Housing, circa 1969-2000s; Archival Resource Key (Box 32, Folder 1-2)